## **JORGE SARRICOLEA VEYRO**

Full-Stack developer with more than 2 years of experience. I am a Personal Finance and Technology enthusiast, always keeping up with the latest trends.











## About me

+2 years ago, I embarked on my journey in web development, creating attractive and functional web applications. My focus is on merging technical skills with a keen eye for design, which drives me to constantly advance. I firmly believe that true changes requires order, discipline, and perseverance, which are essential for achieving success.

# **Experience**

## **Datamatic Software**

Web Developer | 2022 -2022

I worked on different projects, designing the user interface from scratch, adding new features and reusable components for various projects.

## **Jumwork**

Web Developer | 2018 -2022

I designed the whole brand, UX/UI design from scratch on Bubble. Integration with Stripe API and others in backend process. Worked with different plugins, like Sendgrid and upgraded old pages to the new responsive engine.

## Education

Instituto Tecnológico de Mérida | 2020 - Present

Computer Stystems Engineer

# **Projects**

#### THE MOVIES APP

#### [7 [7] **JUMWORK**

The Movies APP is a platform designed to view information about the most popular, highest-rated, and upcoming movies. The information is obtained from TheMovieDB API.

I designed the whole brand, UX/UI design from scratch on Bubble. Integration with Stripe API and others in backend process. Worked with different plugins, like Sendgrid and upgraded old pages to the new responsive engine.

۲.

The Spotify clone, non-functional, is just the user interface of the desktop application's home page. It is not responsive. The idea behind this project is to showcase my pixel-perfect skills. This is a small search engine with simulated Google-like recommendations, the intention is to demonstrate my UI skills.

## **WEATHER APP**

**四** 

ROCK, PAPER OR SCISSORS ☑ 🗘

When working with REST APIs, the ideal project to practice is to make a weather app. I have used the free OpenWeatherMap API. The design is minimalist, and I have used the icons that this API contains.

The famous Rock, Paper, Scissors game, play against the computer and win?...

Designed to be responsive and simple.

### **RECIPIES NET**

**2** 0

**CALORIE CALCULATOR** 

**2** 0

This is a recipe search engine obtained through the MealDB API. It features an attractive and responsive user interface that allows users to search for a wide variety of culinary recipes. This is a calorie intake calculator designed to help users determine their daily caloric needs based on their level of physical activity. It features a user-friendly and responsive design that makes it easy for individuals to calculate their ideal caloric intake.

## **Skills**

